const e="apes_ch21",o="Chapter 21",s=[{number:1,question:"Generally, there is no waste in nature.",choices:["True","False"],correct:0},{number:2,question:"Wastes that threaten human health or the environment because they are poisonous, dangerously chemically reactive, corrosive, or flammable are",choices:["industrial wastes.","solid wastes.","hazardous wastes.","municipal wastes."],correct:2},{number:3,question:"The country that produces the greatest amount of solid waste is",choices:["Mexico.","the United States.","Japan.","China."],correct:1},{number:4,question:"Most of New York City's garbage is",choices:["burned.","recycled.","buried.","exported out of state."],correct:3},{number:5,question:"Reducing the environmental impact of municipal solid waste without trying to reduce the amount of waste produced is known as",choices:["recycling.","reusing.","waste management.","waste reduction."],correct:2},{number:6,question:"Which of the following methods best addresses the amount of virgin materials used by consumers?",choices:["all of the choices","reusing","recycling","reducing"],correct:3},{number:7,question:"Which of the following methods of waste reduction is the most effective?",choices:["reusing","none of the choices","reducing","recycling"],correct:2},{number:8,question:"The best option for bagging groceries is to use",choices:["paper bags.","plastic bags.","reusable cloth bags.","all of the choices."],correct:2},{number:9,question:"Turning materials into new products of the same type is known as",choices:["primary recycling.","reducing.","secondary recycling.","reusing."],correct:0},{number:10,question:"Wastes produced in manufacturing processes are",choices:["preconsumer.","external.","never able to be recycled.","postconsumer."],correct:0},{number:11,question:"Using bacteria to break down food and other organic wastes is known as",choices:["closed-loop recycling.","composting.","reusing.","secondary recycling."],correct:1},{number:12,question:"By providing more access to electronic information, the internet has reduced the amount of paper used in the United States.",choices:["False","True"],correct:0},{number:13,question:"________ consists of various types of large polymers, or resins, produced mostly from oil and natural gas.",choices:["Paper","Steel","Plastic","Aluminum"],correct:2},{number:14,question:"Burning wastes in incinerators provides all of the following benefits except",choices:["reduces volume of wastes.","can generate energy.","causes little water pollution.","adds pollutants to the atmosphere."],correct:3},{number:15,question:"Most solid wastes in the United States are disposed of",choices:["by incineration.","by recycling.","in sanitary landfills.","in open dumps."],correct:2},{number:16,question:"Which of the following correctly prioritizes how to deal with hazardous wastes?",choices:["Convert as much as possible to less hazardous substances; put in long-term, safe storage.","Produce less; convert as much as possible to less hazardous substances.","Produce less; convert as much as possible to less hazardous substances; put in long-term, safe storage.","Convert as much as possible to less hazardous substances; put in long-term, safe storage; produce less."],correct:2},{number:17,question:"Hazardous wastes may be detoxified by which of the following methods?",choices:["chemical","physical","biological","all of the choices"],correct:3},{number:18,question:"The most common method of dealing with hazardous wastes is by",choices:["burial.","bioremediation.","incineration.","phytoremediation."],correct:0},{number:19,question:"________, a highly toxic pollutant, was phased out of gasoline in the United States during the 1970s.",choices:["Carbon monoxide","Mercury","Lead","Ozone"],correct:2},{number:21,question:"Protecting everyone from environmental hazards regardless of race, gender, age, national origin, income, social class, or any political factor, falls under",choices:["environmental justice.","the Superfund Program.","comprehensive environmental response, compensation, and liability.","the Clean Water Act."],correct:0}],t={id:e,displayName:o,questions:s};export{t as default,o as displayName,e as id,s as questions};
